{"data":[{"question":"It was suggested that each traveler ___ enough clothes on the trip.","a":"brought","b":"bring","c":"had better bring","d":"would bring","answer":"2","explain":"\n- The Subjunctive is used to emphasize urgency or importance. It is used after certain expressions: \n - S+ advise \/ask\/to command\/demand\/desire\/insist\/propose\/recommend\/request\/suggest\/ urge (that) + S + (would) Infinitive ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"69","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"},{"question":"The president of the country gave the order that the whole nation ___ to go out at night.","a":"should not be allowed","b":"shouldn't allow","c":"mustn't be allowed","d":"not be allowed","answer":"1","explain":"\n- The Subjunctive is used to emphasize urgency or importance. It is used after certain expressions:\n -S+ advise \/ask\/to command\/demand\/desire\/insist\/propose\/recommend\/request\/suggest\/ urge (that) + S + (would) Infinitive","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"69","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"},{"question":"Doris's father insisted Doris ___ a rich man.","a":"be engaged to","b":"would be engaged to","c":"must be engaged to","d":"should engage to","answer":"1","explain":"\n- The Subjunctive is used to emphasize urgency or importance. It is used after certain expressions: \n - S+ advise \/ask\/to command\/demand\/desire\/insist\/propose\/recommend\/request\/suggest\/ urge (that) + S + (would) Infinitive","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"69","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"},{"question":"Mr. Brown\u00a0acts that way as if he ___ a foreigner.","a":"should be","b":"is","c":"were","d":"had been","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Clauses that start with as if\/as though express unreality, improbability or doubt if they are followed by an unreal tense \n- The simple past tense is used if we talk about an unreal situation in the present","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"69","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"},{"question":"He may even request that such an evil law ___.","a":"not be passed","b":"will be passed","c":"mustn't be passed","d":"would be passed","answer":"1","explain":"\n- The Subjunctive is used to emphasize urgency or importance. It is used after certain expressions: \n - S+ advise \/ask\/to command\/demand\/desire\/insist\/propose\/recommend\/request\/suggest\/ urge (that) + S + (would) Infinitive ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"69","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"},{"question":"Jack didn't come yesterday, or you ___ him.","a":"were to see","b":"would see","c":"had seen","d":"might have seen","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Might have PP: used to say that something was a possibility in the past but did not actually happen ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"69","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"},{"question":"The writer ___ her job well, but she ___ so careless.","a":"could do, was","b":"had done, had been","c":"hadn't done, had been","d":"could have done, was","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Could have PP: used to say that something was a possibility in the past, but did not actually happen \n- Could have pp, simple past ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"69","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"},{"question":"The Chairperson demanded the survey ___ by the end of the next week.","a":"should complete","b":"be completed","c":"would be completed","d":"was completed","answer":"2","explain":"\n- The Subjunctive is used to emphasize urgency or importance. It is used after certain expressions: \n - S+ advise \/ask\/to command\/demand\/desire\/insist\/propose\/recommend\/request\/suggest\/ urge (that) + S + (would) Infinitive \n- Passive voice: -S+ advise \/ask\/to command\/demand... (that) S + be + PP","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"69","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"},{"question":"___ it rain tomorrow, we would have to put off the visit to the farm .","a":"Should","b":"Were","c":"Will","d":"Would","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Sometimes conditional forms are inverted as a means of sounding more formal. In this case, the conditional 'if' is dropped and the inverted forms takes the place of the 'if clause' \n- Inversion clause: auxiliary + subject + main verb","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"69","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"},{"question":"If my car ___ out of gas, I would have arrived there.","a":"shouldn't run","b":"didn't run","c":"hadn't run","d":"haven't run","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Conditional Sentence Type 3: used to talk about things that didn't happened in the past and the consequence if they had happened \n+ Form: if + Past Perfect, would + have + Past Participle ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"69","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"}]}